[*] GKFlasher v1.0.99
[*] Selected protocol: kline. Initializing..
[*] Trying to start diagnostic session
[*] Set timing parameters to maximum
[*] Security Access
[*] Trying to identify ECU automatically.. 
[*] Found! SIMK43 V6 4mbit (5WY17)
[*] Trying to find calibration..
[*] Found! Description: ca654019, calibration: G5J7TS0A
[*] Attempting privilege escalation with the IOCLID patch
[!] Patch likely not present, failed to escalate privileges.
    Read will only include the calibration and program zones.
    If you're running ca663056, feel encouraged to apply the IOCLID patch.
    It will allow you to read the whole memory over OBD2, just like BSL.
    You can find it at https://github.com/OpenGK-org/opengk-simk
[*] Reading from 0x80000 to 0x100000
